amzgame.com 2015-12-10

# Play free popular MMO& RPG browser games on AMZGame.com

AMZGames is committed to protecting your privacy and creating a strong relationship with our users. This privacy policy explains the use of personal information collected via (i) our websites, whether at www.amzgame.com or other uniform resource locators (URLs) owned or operated by us, and (ii) our products and services, including without limitation those that we provide via our websites, other third party platforms, and desktop and mobile applications (collectively, all of the foregoing in clauses (i) and (ii) are referred to as our "Services").  
This policy does not apply to (a) the practices of companies that we do not own or control, (b) people that we do not employ or manage, (c) third party websites, whether linked to or from our Services, (d) information that you provide to us for purposes of seeking employment, provision of services to us, business proposals or similar matters, (e) information that you provide to us unsolicited, or (f) information that we collect offline.  
As used in this Privacy Policy, "personal information" means information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, e-mail address, phone number or physical address. 

### INformation Collection And Use

Our primary goal in collecting personal is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Site and to deliver better services, products, and more relevant content to our customers, prospective customers, and visitors. We may collect personal information by any of the following methods.  
Mailing List Member: If you choose to provide us personal information in order to subscribe to our mailing list or newsletter, we may collect information to aid delivery and preferences such as e-mail address and message performance statistics.  
Registered Site Member: If you choose to register on our Site, we may track broad site usage information as well as aggregate usage of website community features such as downloads and forums. This is in addition to the personal data collected during the registration process.  
Promotions: We may collect information to aid in any promotions or prizes offered by our Site.  
Game Software: If you install or use any of the game software offered by our Site, we collect and aggregate a variety of data to monitor system and simulation performance, and to verify your unique identity. This may include specific and general information about your computer hardware and Internet connection, which are stored together but are not personally identifiable. This is in addition to the personal data and other personal information collected during the registration process.  
Payment Transaction: If any payment transaction occurs on our Site, we collect information about such transaction, including credit card numbers or other billing information. 

### Special Circumstances

Former Customer: If you cease being a registered user with our Site, we will keep a copy of your registration file in our database for use in the event you wish to rejoin our service.  
Response to Job Postings or Unsolicited Communications: Please note that information we receive in reference to a job posting or via unsolicited communications do not fall under the scope of this Privacy Policy. However, information from your resume will be used solely for the purpose of evaluating your candidacy for employment. 

### Voluntary Disclosure Of Personal Information

You may choose to disclose personal information in our online community features, blogs, in-game chats or other public forums, directly to other users while using the Site service.  
Please be aware that such information is public information and you should not expect privacy or confidentiality under these circumstances. AMZGame shall not be liable in any way for such disclosure of personal information. 

### Use Of Personal Data

We use your personal information for operational purposes only. For example, we may use your information to send you administrative communications either about your account with us or about features of our Site, including any changes to this Privacy Policy. Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. We attempt to limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.  
We use e-mail addresses to fulfill requests for services. For example, mailing addresses are used for the delivery of prizes. Occasionally, we share your personal information (e.g., e-mail address) with a third party sponsor, co-sponsor, or other reputable third party that provides products or services that may be of interest to you. We may occasionally employ other companies to perform services necessary for our internal operations, such as companies that personalize our web pages, process credit card transactions, analyze customers' interaction with our Site, and process consumer surveys.  
Finally, we may take your personal information and make it non-personally identifiable. We do this either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (e.g., your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. Given the non-personal nature of this information, no restrictions apply under this Privacy Policy on our right to de-personalize your personal information. We may use de-personalized information in any way and share it with third parties without your consent. 

### Required Disclosures

We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law (e.g., court order or subpoena) or such disclosure helps enforce   
(i) our Terms of Use, contests, sweepstakes, promotions, or game rules; (ii) protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of your property; or (iii) protect the safety and security of our website or third parties. 

### Age Requirement

AMZGame will not knowingly collect, use or retain personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13, for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing or promotional purposes).   
We request that any child under the age of 13 who wishes to use the Site obtain the permission of his/her parent or guardian. 

### Modification Of Privacy Policy

We may periodically update and modify our privacy policy to reflect changes in the types of information we collect, the means we use to collect information, and/or our usage of collected information.   
If we update the policy, we will publish the updated policy here You are responsible for periodically checking back here to review our Privacy Policy.
